Episode 19:  Black Flash
Are you all right, Inumaki-senpai?
Salmon.
Here it comes!
Stop.
Convergence!
Piercing Blood!
He wounded it?
So he wasn't serious at all
when he fought me, then?
Hurry! He's just gonna heal right away!
Inumaki will stop it,
we'll attack, and then
we'll get away from it.
Then we repeat that as we
try to get outside this veil
and rejoin the principal and the others.
But there's no telling when the
current balance will fall apart.
His cursed speech isn't
affecting it much anyway,
and we're not getting a chance
to contact the teachers.
If it figures out how to deal with
his cursed speech, we're finished.
Hurry!
We don't know what
the cursed spirit's after.
There's a chance the principal and
the other sorcerers stationed at
Jujutsu Tech haven't taken action.
I'd like to quickly rejoin Toudou,
or at the very least, Miwa, but...
Inumaki-senpai will stop it.
Don't worry! Just go!
St—
He's the one hitting his limit first?!
Are you alive, Kamo-san?
He wasn't using powerful words,
but it still destroyed his throat.
It's just that much stronger!
Mustard leaf.
Inumaki-senpai...
That's enough!
Blast away!
You can't cut me with that dull blade.
Its eye trees are more
fragile than the rest!
Now this sword isn't so bad.
I have something even better.
This one feels disgusting to use, though.
"Cursed tools" refers to
weapons imbued with curses.
Based on their force and effects,
they're divided into grades one
through four, just like sorcerers.
The higher a cursed tool's grade,
the greater the advantage it
provides in jujutsu combat.
Megumi, make absolutely
sure you don't lose that.
I won't lose it.
If you sold it, you'd get
at least five billion for it.
Huh?
Special-grade cursed tool:
Playful Cloud!
Indeed, that is a good weapon.
Demon Dog...
With the exception of my expanded
technique, Bottomless Well,
if any of my ten shikigami
are completely destroyed,
I can never manifest them again.
However, the power and techniques
of the destroyed shikigami
are passed on to the others.
...Totality!
It's fast.
It's trying to take off
my wounded arm first?
The sorcerer boy is in the forest...
The boy's sword!
Maki-san!
Please don't ever make me use
that three-section staff again!
It's too hard to use!
It's handy once you get used—
Megumi!
Maki-san!
Damn it! All because I screwed up!
My strike was aimed for your heart.
What a wonderful reaction.
Jujutsu sorcerers are
extraordinarily compassionate.
An opening is always created
when their ally is injured.
It's destroyed?!
No, Megumi released the technique!
You shouldn't use cursed techniques anymore.
The bud embedded in you loves cursed energy.
The more you use techniques, the deeper
its roots will extend into your body.
How kind of you to warn me.
You're planning to kill us anyway, though.
Apparently, it works faster
when I explain it.
You move well.
But you're missing the edge you had earlier.
Wring out that cursed energy,
even if it rips my stomach open!
I'm not like everyone else.
I choose who I protect.
I shoulder the least responsibility!
Therefore...
I'm not allowed to fall before anyone else!
Megumi, stop!
Our job is done.
It's time to tag out.
You good to go, my friend?
Yeah!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
So heavy...
I can't believe these two
were beaten this badly.
We're counting on you, Toudou-kun.
Your strength is the one thing
you've got going for you.
Stop, Itadori!
That's not something we can han—
Panda.
Yeah?
Take those two and exit the veil.
According to Nishimiya,
this is an anti-Gojou Satoru veil,
so we can come and go without issue.
Wait! Even you can't—
Fushiguro.
It's okay.
Please.
Looks like you've realized it.
Nobody is allowed to touch those
who have started growing wings.
And that's exactly where
Itadori stands right now.
If you die again, I'll kill you myself!
Okay, let's go.
Pandash!
Guess I can't afford to die now.
I won't lift a finger to help,
Itadori.
Not until you land a Black Flash.
If you can't land a Black Flash,
then I'll just watch you die,
no matter what happens to you.
Got it!
Sukuna's vessel and... Who is that man?
He has a certain presence,
but the amount of cursed energy he possesses
is most definitely less than mine.
However, he has that mysterious brazenness.
He must have quite the technique,
since I couldn't move carelessly before him.
And what is this "Black Flash"?
So, how will they attack?
You can talk?
There's something I want to ask you.
Are you allied with
a humanoid cursed spirit
who has a patchwork face?
And if I say I am?
He didn't carelessly close the distance.
I commend him for that.
He's fast!
He has more explosive power
than the earlier girl!
However, its intensity is poor.
Its torso's wide open!
It's letting its guard down because I held back.
I can land it now!
Black Flash!
Damn it!
My friend.
Anger is an important trigger for sorcerers.
Sometimes they can be taken down
purely because they accidentally
angered their foe.
And the opposite is also true.
Sometimes they lose because their
own anger disrupts their cursed energy,
so they can't exercise their abilities.
Your friend has been wounded,
and worse yet, they've rained on your
honeymoon with me, your best friend,
so I can really understand
why you'd be boiling with rage.
But that rage is too much for you.
Put it away for now.
Are they fighting each other?
Are those stray thoughts gone now?
Yeah, not a single one left.
Thank you so much, best friend!
Black Flash.
It's a distortion of space born
from the impact of cursed energy
delivered within a trillionth
of a second of a blow.
It delivers 2.5 times the
force of a normal strike.
There are no sorcerers who can
consistently use Black Flash.
However...
Between those who have experienced
Black Flash and those who have not,
their distance from the core of cursed energy
is like that of Heaven from Earth.
What tremendous concentration...
The instant cursed energy impacts
within a trillionth of a second of a blow,
space is distorted...
and cursed energy flashes black.
Black Flash!
Wha—
He's grown.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
That was... Black Flash?
What?
This is my cursed energy, right?
Now you understand
the taste of cursed energy.
Up until now,
you've just been throwing an
ingredient you've never tasted before
into a pot and boiling it
without knowing why.
But after experiencing Black Flash
and understanding the taste of
your ingredient, your cursed energy,
you stand on a completely different level
as a chef than you did three seconds ago.
Congratulations, brother.
You can become strong.
I had heard that Sukuna's vessel
was immature as a sorcerer,
but he and this mysterious man...
Something about them is different
from the other masses.
It can heal?!
A cursed spirit's body is made
up of cursed energy.
Unlike us, they don't need any advanced
reversed cursed technique to heal.
An injury like that is
nothing to a special-grade.
But there's no doubt that it
shaves away their cursed energy,
and if you crush their head, it's game-set.
Now, shall we get cooking?
It would seem that
I should take you two somewhat seriously.
What a wide range of attack!
Don't falter!
That range means its force
and speed are weaker!
That hit hard!
Their blows aren't as bad as
that flashy black one before,
but each one possesses enough
force to steadily damage me!
Toudou! Let's match our timing better!
Yeah!
Our footing!
I messed up!
I thought it was passing cursed
energy through real objects
to manipulate that much mass!
But it's all the embodiment—
the manifestation of its cursed energy!
That's a special-grade for you!
Learn how great the land is!
Attacking while we fall? That's brutal!
However...
Brother!
They dodged that?!
But what...
What is this feeling?!
You know, Hanami,
you should be more honest.
I don't believe I'm faking anything.
I don't mean to call you a liar.
I know why you're fighting.
But it's the process.
You should enjoy the battles,
the present, much more.
Do you enjoy them?
Well, yeah.
Though...
It was only recently that the joy and pleasure
I feel in battle became my motive.
Before I knew it, I was tricking,
deceiving, and murdering,
and before I knew it, I felt fulfilled.
Just as humans eat, sleep, and screw,
I think that's a curse's instinct.
We may have gained reason,
but that doesn't justify
going against our instincts.
The soul is a blend of instinct and reason.
No one can say anything
about an individual's ratio.
But your soul's a little constrained.
Hanami, you're actually...
much stronger, aren't you?
Ow...
Toudou!
I'm fine!
It just expended so much cursed energy!
Now's our chance to strike!
You monster!
Mahito, right now...
I'm enjoying a fight!
You okay, brother?!
No problemo!
Excellent!
Then it's time to unleash my technique!
Juju Stroll
Coat rack!
Going to make a great coat rack!
Hey, what kind of coat rack
would Gojou Satoru be?
Probably a standing coat rack.
I'd use his hip bone with the sacral bone
and coccyx as the base for the stand,
then rework his femurs and
use them to stabilize it.
I'd use his spine's lumbar vertebrae,
thoracic vertebrae,
and up to the third cervical vertebrae.
To give it more height... let's see...
Ancient camphor wood would be good.
I could alternate ancient camphor replicas
with the bones to accentuate the height.
Then I'd extend the spinous process
and transverse process based on the
overall balance to create the hangers.
I'd do that by grafting on
more ancient camphor.
Depending on the coloring, it could be good
to cover the skull with tanned hide.
Nice! Very nice!
I'll be able to make a great coat rack!
No one needs it.
Episode 20:
Nonstandard